

9

Orange County, California

linkedin.com/in/tammyle245

6

(909) 767-9995

le\_t\_create@yahoo.com letam245.github.io



github.com/letam245

## PROFILE

Mobile Developer specializing in Native Applications and Softwares Development with professional background in UX-UI Design. Experienced in building modern, mobile responsive, user friendly interfaces and functionalapplications all the way from wireframes to rollout. Adept at researching and analyzing user experience and project requirements/needs. Strong background in interpersonal communication, problem solving and people assisting.



#### **EDUCATION**

2017

# CERTIFICATION IN FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT

UCI Division of Continuing Education

2012 - 2015

#### **B.F.A. IN GRAPHIC DESIGN**

Minor in Marketing Management

Cal Poly Pomona



## **SKILLS**

#### **Programming Languages:**

HTML | CSS | LESS | SASS | Bootstrap
JavaScript | jQuery | Xcode | Vue | Vuetify
React | React Native | Swift | Node |
NPM | JSON | AJAX | RESTful API's | Git
Heroku | MongoDB | MySQL | Sequelize
MVC | MVVC | Express Handlebar |
Firebase | Cocoapods

#### Design:

Photoshop | Illustrator | Dreamweaver InDesign | After Effect | Adobe Acrobat AdobeXD | Sketch | Invision | Xcode



### **EXPERIENCE**

04/2018 - Present - Tom Ferry International

#### LEAD MOBILE DEVELOPER | UI/UX DEVELOPER

- + Partner with other developers, marketing department and IT support team in Agile environment to create/maintain templates/library of reusable codes and troubleshoot to find effective solutions that will improve users experience on the company internal illum website <a href="https://tfservices-staging.tomferry.com">https://tfservices-staging.tomferry.com</a>
- + Transfer wireframe/prototypes created in AdobeXD to full-functional and complex iOS/Android applications using Swift 4.2, Xcode, third-party Cocoapods, NPM packages React, React Natives, Firebase APIs for crashlytics & push notification (illum iOS & Android app can be downloaded on <a href="AppStore">AppStore</a> and <a href="GooglePlay">GooglePlay</a>)
- + Participate in web applications development and system design process to apply new technologies, languages and frameworks (Vue.js, Vuetify, Axios, APIs, NPM packages) in order to expand and enhance users networking and data tracking on HUB website with efficient and helpful tools/features such as referral network and roleplay videos <a href="https://referrals-staging.tomferry.com/">https://referrals-staging.tomferry.com/</a> & <a href="https://roleplays-staging.tomferry.com/">https://roleplays-staging.tomferry.com/</a>
- + Work with Bootstrap4, CSS, SASS, HTML, Webpack, Laravel, Javascript, Jquery and MVVC architectural pattern to convert static mock-ups/wireframes into semantic, responsive, cross-browser web pages following best practices and design patterns.
- + Extract and create necessary assets from Photoshop and Illustrator files to ensure consistent styling, branding graphic standards throughout the product interfaces.

05/2018 - Present — *Trilogy Education - UCI Division of Continuing Education* **SUBTITUTE TEACHING ASSISTANT** 

+ Assist students in UI/UX and Full-stack Web Development cohorts with insightful feedback and guidance on their coding exercises and designing projects.

09/2016 - 03/2018 - OASIS Medical Inc.

#### WEB & GRAPHIC DESIGNER | MARKETING COORDINATOR

- + Design, update, manage web and digital collaterals to expand product lines, features for the company's E-commerce websites using Bootstrap, HTML, CSS, Javascript, jQuery integrated with Telerik Sitefinity CMS Platform (written in .NET framework <a href="https://www.oasistears.com">www.oasistears.com</a> | <a href="https://www.oasistears.com">www.oasistears.com</a> |
- + Work closely with customer service team and JDE specialists to provide support, maintenance and solutions for web bugs/issues. Increasing customers satisfaction and saving thousand of dollars on third party IT consultant expense.
- + Maintain, update, organize company intranet site (built with customized Wordpress templates and plugins) to generate internal shared documents and communication.
- + Attract more than 100 participants for company webinar series with mobile responsive and cross-browsers compatible email campaigns coded with XHTML, CSS, Mailchimp.
- + Apply company standards, guidelines and documenting procedures to successfully promote new products and events with consistent letterhead/business card/logo design, effective flyers/infographics, appealing trade-show booth displays/assets, engaging web landing pages and animated digital banner ads.
- + Communicate with stakeholders, organizations, sale representatives and customers to gather information and feedbacks to create/edit photos-videos-marketing materials to support and promote company's domestic/international events.